<resources>
    <string name="app_name">gizoogler</string>
    <string name="gizoogle_label">Gizoogle</string>
    <string name="barack">Barack Hussein Obizzay Pt II (/bəˈrɑːk huːˈseɪn oʊˈbɑːmə/ (Bout dis sound listen) bə-RAHK hoo-SAYN oh-BAH-mə;[1][2] born August 4, 1961) be a retired Gangsta sucka whoz ass served as tha 44th Prezzy of tha United Hoodz from 2009 ta 2017. Da first African Gangsta ta assume tha presidency, he previously served as a United Hoodz Senator, representin Illinois from 2005 ta 2008 yo. Dude also served up in tha Illinois State Senate from 1997 ta 2004. Obama started doin thangs up in 1961 up in Honolulu, Hawaii, two muthafuckin years afta tha territory was admitted ta tha Union as tha 50th state. Raised largely up in Hawaii, Obizzay also dropped one year of his childhood up in Washington State n' four muthafuckin years up in Indonesia fo' realz. Afta graduatin from Columbia Universitizzle up in New York Citizzle up in 1983, da thug hit dat shiznit as a cold-ass lil hood organizer up in Chicago. In 1988 Obizzay enrolled up in Harvard Law School, where da thug was tha straight-up original gangsta black prez of tha Harvard Law Review fo' realz. Afta graduation, his thugged-out lil' punk-ass became a cold-ass lil civil muthafuckin rights attorney n' pimp, n' taught constipationizzle law all up in tha Universitizzle of Chicago Law School from 1992 ta 2004. Obizzay represented tha 13th District fo' three terms up in tha Illinois Senate from 1997 ta 2004, when he ran fo' tha U.S. Right back up in yo muthafuckin ass. Senate. Obizzay received nationistic attention up in 2004 wit his unexpected March primary win, his well-received July Democratic Nationizzle Convention keynote address, n' his fuckin landslide November erection ta tha Senate. In 2008, Obizzay was nominated fo' prez a year afta his campaign fuckin started n' afta a cold-ass lil close primary campaign against Hillary Clinton. I aint talkin' bout chicken n' gravy biatch yo. Dude was erected over Republican Jizzy McCain n' was inaugurated on January 20, 2009. Nine months later, Obizzay was named tha 2009 Nobel Peace Prize laureate, acceptin tha award wit tha caveat dat he felt there was others "far mo' deservin of dis honor than I." </string>

</resources>
